#### Contact

robinsonlal1997@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/robinsonlal (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Data Analysis

Customer Relationship Management (CRM)

Communication

#### **Publications**

Design and Fabrication of Low-Cost Detachable Power Unit for a Wheelchair

# Robinson Lal

SPS Associate at Amazon | Telus International | Testbook | Freelancer

India

## Summary

Hey everyone,

I'm an Associate at Amazon's Support Operations, committed to ensuring smooth, hassle-free experiences for selling partners.

I also like graphic designing, video editing and a bit of < coding />.

I'm always ready for challenges that help me learn and grow.

◆ Check out my blog - https://letsreadscripture.blogspot.com/

### Experience

#### Amazon

SPS Associate

July 2023 - Present (1 year 9 months)

We combine technical solutions with personal assistance to meet our selling partners where they're at in their journey.

#### **TELUS International AI Data Solutions**

**SME** 

March 2023 - May 2023 (3 months)

SMEs in India analyse the

relevancy and accuracy of ads and other content on social media. These ads are

specifically targeted to various combinations of market demographics based on gender identity, age range, and social media activity.

#### Testbook

Senior Counselor

October 2022 - March 2023 (6 months)

# Heavy Engineering Corporation Limited, Ranchi

Trainee

June 2018 - June 2018 (1 month)

Ranchi, Jharkhand, India

Learned Forging, Casting, Heat Treatment and Machining at various plants like Foundary Forge Plant, Heavy Machine Building Plant, Heavy Machine Tool Plant.

Indo Danish Tool Room

1 month

**Industrial Trainee** 

January 2018 - January 2018 (1 month)

Jamshedpur, Jharkhand, India

Learned to operate CNC Milling Machine.

**Industrial Trainee** 

January 2018 - January 2018 (1 month)

Jamshedpur, Jharkhand, India

Learned to operate CNC TURNING MACHINE.

Diesel Locomotive Works Varanasi

Trainee

June 2017 - June 2017 (1 month)

Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India

Visited various workshops like TSM, EES, HTS and HMS.

### Education

Sam Higginbottom University of Agriculture, Technology And Sciences (SHUATS)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Mechanical Engineering · (2015 - 2019)